Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=خارج الحلقة=
=Episode 24=
=الحلقة 24=
Are we there?
هل نحن هناك؟
Almost.
بالكاد.
Let me help you sit down, Godmother.
دعيني أساعدك على الجلوس، يا عرابتي.
(Today, I wish to fulfill that filial duty on her behalf.)
(اليوم، أود أن أقوم بهذا الواجب الأبوي نيابة عنها.)
(This might be her first attempt at painting.)
(قد تكون هذه محاولتها الأولى في الرسم.)
(Her very first portrait was of you.)
(كانت صورتها الأولى لك.)
In her mind,
في عقلها،
you must be the one she loved the most.
لا بد وأنك أنت الشخص الذي أحبته أكثر من غيره.
And this.
و هذا.
She bought this for you
لقد اشترت لك هذا
after her adult ceremony.
بعد حفل بلوغها.
(I can only promise)
(لا أستطيع إلا أن أعدك)
(when you're in danger,)
(عندما تكون في خطر)
(I will certainly save you.)
(سوف انقذك بالتأكيد.)
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
Madam Hong, Mr. Song.
السيدة هونغ، السيد سونغ.
Forgive me.
سامحني.
Mother,
الأم،
please stop forcing Miss Yu to marry me.
من فضلك توقف عن إجبار الآنسة يو على الزواج مني.
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished♪
♪العهد هو عزيز ♪
If the City Lord ever mistreats you,
إذا أساء سيد المدينة معاملتك يومًا ما،
tell me and I'll deal with him.
أخبرني وسوف أتعامل معه.
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished♪
♪العهد هو عزيز ♪
♪This endless yearning♪
♪هذا الشوق الذي لا ينتهي♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
(I once imagined)
(تخيلت ذات مرة)
(we were just ordinary folks.)
(كنا مجرد أشخاص عاديين.)
(You and the Madam would have children.)
(أنت والسيدة سيكون لديكما أطفال).
(The man)
(الرجل)
(who cares about the people)
(من يهتم بالناس)
(is my true beloved.)
(هو حبيبي الحقيقي.)
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers♪
♪همسات الذاكرة♪
♪Dreams or illusion♪
♪أحلام أم وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You remain so distant♪
♪أنت تبقى بعيدًا جدًا♪
♪Yet stand before my eyes♪
♪ولكن تقف أمام عيني♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
Wan, I've made arrangements.
وان، لقد اتخذت الترتيبات.
If I don't return,
إذا لم أعود،
Liu Bingmo will send you away.
ليو بينغمو سوف يرسلك بعيدا.
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
Nonsense. You'll definitely come back.
كلام فارغ. ستعود بالتأكيد.
I'll wait for you forever.
سأنتظرك إلى الأبد.
Even if I'm gone,
حتى لو رحلت
promise me you'll live well.
وعدني بأنك ستعيش حياة جيدة.
No sadness. No tears.
لا حزن. لا دموع.
You know
أنت تعرف
I love seeing you smile.
أحب رؤيتك تبتسم.
This time,
هذه المرة،
the last thing I can do for you
آخر شيء يمكنني فعله لك
is to keep you safe.
هو الحفاظ على سلامتك.
Wan.
فان.
Promise me
وعدني
you'll live well.
سوف تعيش حياة جيدة.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
This is the nuptial wine
هذا هو النبيذ الزفافي
you owed me from our wedding day.
لقد كنت مدينًا لي منذ يوم زفافنا.
Now, you'll make it right.
الآن، سوف تفعل ذلك بشكل صحيح.
Okay.
تمام.
If peace is restored and the land is tranquil,
إذا عاد السلام وأصبحت الأرض هادئة،
I vow to grow old with you
أقسم أن أكبر معك
and create a prosperous era.
وخلق عصر مزدهر.
If we lose the war amid endless bloodshed,
إذا خسرنا الحرب وسط سفك الدماء الذي لا ينتهي،
I'll use my own body as a shield
سأستخدم جسدي كدرع
to preserve your smile.
للحفاظ على ابتسامتك.
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
I'll await your return.
سأنتظر عودتك.
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪
Men! Charge!
الرجال! اهجموا!
Advance!
يتقدم!
Yunhao!
يونهاو!
Wan!
فان!
Who did this? Wei Feng!
من فعل هذا؟ وي فينج!
The leader's dead. Retreat!
لقد مات القائد. تراجعوا!
This sword strike
هذه ضربة السيف
is vengeance for the people
هو الانتقام للشعب
you slaughtered.
لقد ذبحت.
Yunqing.
يونتشينغ.
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished♪
♪العهد هو عزيز ♪
♪This endless yearning♪
♪هذا الشوق الذي لا ينتهي♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
(One year later)
(بعد عام واحد)
Wan, it's lantern festival again.
وان، إنه مهرجان الفوانيس مرة أخرى.
Our lantern is the best, isn't it?
فانوسنا هو الأفضل، أليس كذلك؟
Did you hear it, Wan?
هل سمعت ذلك وان؟
This way?
من هنا؟
Look.
ينظر.
(The End)
(النهاية)
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪همسات الذاكرة، أحلام أو وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You seem so distant, yet right before my eyes♪
♪تبدو بعيدًا جدًا، ومع ذلك، أمام عيني مباشرة♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪